That's right, guys. Crypto is pumping
while I'm on vacation and I'm up more
than the pump itself. How is that even
possible? I will show you in this video
and also which system I'm using so you
can do the same. And of course, my
entire community is super happy about
this result. As you can see here, why
was it pumping in the first place and do
we need to predict this event in order
to benefit from them? Ethereum pumped
about 19% while my Ethereum position
that you can see right here is up 22.1%.
Solana is up 13% while my Solana
position right here is up 15% already.
But how did the AI strategy even know to
be in these positions before the pump?
Does it know something or was it just
luck? And I also want to show you my
largest profit which is on the pump coin
is 104% profit. Everything is 1x
leverage by the way. And this trade is
super legendary. I will show you that
later. I suggest you stick around until
the end of this short but gamechanging
video where I will show you exactly
which system this is and as well how you
can use it for yourself. And I also hope
that you appreciate the transparency. Me
showing you live positions on my
Hyperlquid account, not just some
reconstruction from the past. But even
with a good system, you need to know how
to use it. And that means you need to
avoid a couple of traps, which I will
also talk about in this video. And to
celebrate our success, we might even
have added a coupon code somewhere in
this video. So get your coffee and pay
attention because this video might
actually change your trading game
forever. And also show some love to this
video. Like it if it adds any value. And
of course consider subscribing to this
channel if you want to learn more about
algorithmic trading with AI so you don't
have to waste your time watching the
charts. Keep in mind this is not
financial advice. Crypto is risky. You
can lose all of your money. Yes. And
today without the glasses because
they're reflecting way too much of the
room that I'm in right now. But anyway,
let's get started. But why did the
crypto market pump so quickly so much
out of nowhere? And the answer is very
simple. The US Treasury made an
announcement. And that announcement,
well, changed everything. They came out
yesterday with a bombshell saying that
they will double down on buying their
own bonds. They will spend more than 4
billion per issue, per bond auction. And
that is double the amount they spent
before, which was 2 billion. But why
does it matter so much for the crypto
market? Well, because it looks like the
government will print as much money as
possible to buy their own bonds to push
the yields down because they cannot
afford to pay such high yields for 30
years. Okay? And that means that they
will print the money because they don't
make enough from taxes, right? Or where
else would they get the money from? And
simply the market expects that there
will be inflation in the dollar and
that's why Bitcoin was created, right?
Because back in the day we bailed out
the banks and now it looks like we're
going to bail out the government.
Bitcoin doesn't need bailout. Bitcoin
cannot be inflated and that is why it's
pumping and it's dragging the entire
crypto market with it. And by the way,
the last time the yields were that high
was one year before the financial
crisis. Oh my god, the reaction from the
market was violent as you have seen in
the charts. The beautiful thing is that
you don't need to predict this which the
entire video proves. The AI strategy was
invested weeks before so that it can
benefit from events like these. Don't
predict, react. And the pump came
literally out of nowhere. Let's play
this back and remove these last two
candles. As you can see, this is how the
chart looked like on Bitcoin. And this
was the local top right here. It didn't
even touch that. It barely broke above
my trend detector line and then suddenly
bam. Right? This is absolute madness.
And so the question is how did my AI
strategy know to be invested in this
before the pump happened? Because that
is how it's able to have more profit
than the pump itself. The reason why it
can do that is because it's running this
prompt with the trading rules every
single day as you can see here for a
while now. So, it had some time to scan
the market by using the trend radar data
which you can see here on my screen. So,
it's basically going through all the
major crypto coins and scanning for
opportunities and entering them whenever
the trading rules allow. And those rules
have triggered a buy on Ethereum as you
can see on my chart on the 3rd of
August. And that was literally 15 days
before the pump itself. So, way early.
No need to read the news fully
automatically. Okay. And that is how
it's able to now benefit from that. And
that is true for a lot of other
positions as you can see here also for
pump. And pump is pumping quite
dramatically. And I entered that one on
the 16th of July. And since then it's in
an uptrend. The AI is holding on to it
because it's a trend following system.
So as long as the trend is going in the
right direction, it's going to hold on
to that position. and is now up 111%
guys. How cool is that? Let's look at
one more coin guys. We are looking at
Solana right here and I'm on a 1 hour
chart so I can show you much better when
it entered. So you can see here 18th of
August beginning of the day and that is
how it was able to capture the entire
move here 14.73%.
And when we go to Trading View and we
check out how much the pump actually
was, you can see that it was 12.9%.
meaning that in order to get the
performance that I have right now, you
have to enter before the pump, which is
exactly what happened. Was it luck or
does the strategy know something? Now,
in order to answer that question, let me
show you the equity line of this
strategy of this portfolio in the last
30 days. And as you can see here, it was
not really immediately in profit. As you
can see here, it went up, it went down.
there was a draw down of 2.72% which in
hindsight you don't care about but while
using this strategy and seeing it go
sideways for so long which by the way
the entire crypto market went sideways
as well I had to endure the entire
sideways move and stay allocated and
automated so I can be ready like a lion
to strike when the opportunity comes and
that is how I was early and I was there
before the pump of course the market
went sideways and my portfolio also went
sideways. That's fine. But when the
market goes up, I want to be in the
opportunities. And as you can see here,
I have 25 positions. Actually, I think
now it's 26 positions that are in
profit. And as you can see here, the
pump position went even higher while
recording this video. In fact, my entire
portfolio went higher while cutting this
video. And that is why I think this is
not luck, guys. This is simply sticking
to a strategy long enough, being
patient, and not freaking out when the
market is boring. In my last video, I
told you guys that I was 95% in cash,
waiting for the right moment to strike,
not fomoing in early. Now, this is the
signal, the AI strategy figured it out.
I think you should have watched that
before to be ready. Watch it after this
video if you want to learn how the game
is played. The link is up top. But there
is still a trap that you can run into.
Even though the strategy is great, but
you might not know how it works and then
you interpret it the wrong way. Let me
show you what I mean. And so if you're
using this strategy or a similar
strategy from my universe, then you have
to understand one thing is that I'm
doing trend following. And that means
that when the strategy closes positions,
that is often because they're not going
in the right direction. So if you look
at the trading history, you will see a
lot of small losing trades, right?
Because the big ones, they are in an
uptrend, okay, or in a downtrend, but in
profit. And the strategy's mission is to
stick to this trade for as long as this
trend continues. Okay, so why would I
sell pump for example if the trend is
still mega strong? I want to stay in the
trade. Okay, there's no reason to close
that. Once it's closed, it will be a
very positive and profitable trade. But
in the meantime, there will be a lot of
small losses because the strategy is
cleaning away all of the nonprofitable
trades fast because small losses are
easy to digest. But if we let the losses
become larger, that would be a problem,
right? And that is why you see a lot of
open positions that are in profit
because their trend is still intact. And
a lot of people don't understand and
they think that the strategy has to
trade every day in a profit. But that's
not the case. What it has to do though,
and that is why I showed you the equity
line, it has to grow your portfolio
value over time. Of course, it needs
time for that because a trend following
system. And that's another trap that a
lot of people fall into because you
cannot make specific amount of money per
month, right? Because it really depends
on the market conditions. Those are the
two traps that a lot of you are falling
into which basically strips away your
chances even to use a strategy like this
which is very profitable. But if you
can't use it long enough, you will not
benefit from it. Okay, Michael, but what
is the trading strategy that you're
using behind you? I want to use the same
one. How can I get access? Well, thanks
for the question. Let me put myself down
there. And the strategy I'm using is on
the strategies page of signnum.money. I
will put the link down below. And I am
an autotrading member because well
that's my VIP program. And so this is
the strategy that I was showing you all
the time in this video. These are the
KPIs and this is the equity line. And
what I'm doing is I just select the bot
I want to use it with. I copy the
prompt. I create a routine in Claude. I
already have it here and this is my
routine and I just paste the prompt in
there. And the prompt has all the rules
for trading the way that it's doing.
Right? And there is a video on my
channel which is pretty popular 100,000
views explaining how to set up your
portfolio automation with clawed
routines. Go and watch it later if you
want to start using this system. It
takes literally 5 minutes and you can
have the same thing running now. The
only thing is that in order to get
access to this particular strategy, you
need to be a member of the autotrading
masterass. You can check out the link
down below autotrading.vip and also
check out the website. Read what it says
there. do your research if you want to
join or not. It's not super cheap to
join, but you can see the results are
very good. And if you don't want to
join, it's totally fine. You can just
create a Signum account and use this
particular strategy, which is built on
the Trend Radar Gshion channel report,
and it's also long short. The KPIs are
less than the ones from the member
strategy, but they're still very good
and it's a great one to start with. You
don't need to join anything, but if you
decide to do so, here is a coupon code
to make it even easier for you. 20% off
with the coupon code AI bull. AI bull
market red bull. You choose, but AI bull
is the code minus 20% when you use it at
checkout. In signum, you will see that
there is a minus 10% already, but simply
go to the checkout and put AI bull and
it will apply 20%. Don't wait too long.
This coupon code will expire at the end
of August. So, if you want to join, do
it now. But first, why not create a
Signum account for free and just set up
the AI strategy that is available to you
right now. You should watch this video
because I'm explaining there step by
step how to do that.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Oh yeah.
>> Strategies. We know what to do. [music]
Yeah. Do. Yeah. Yeah. Stop. Loses
[singing] set. Watch the bus rise
[music] and